Guide to the Margaret Flory Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Margaret Flory Papers
1929-2009
RG 86
Yale University Divinity School Library
62
(148 boxes)
Correspondence, writings, subject files, and collected material document the life and work of Margaret Flory and the many organizations with which she was associated throughout her long career in missions and student work. Margaret Flory was an ecumenist, leader of student religious work, and mission executive in the Presbyterian Church (USA) from 1944-1980 who began and directed innovative missions programs including Junior Year Abroad, Frontier Internships in Mission, and Bi-National Service.
Flory, Margaret
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Margaret Flory.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
1914 May 13 Born in Wauseon, Ohio.
1936 B.A. in English, Ohio University, Athens.
1938 M.A. in Speech and Drama, Ohio University.
1939-40 Taught at Alabama State College for Women, organized Presbyterian Association.
1940-44 Director of the Westminster Foundation, Ohio University.
1940-42 Took summer courses at Union Theological Seminary.
1944 Commissioned as a missionary to China; studied Chinese language at UC Berkeley.
1944-50 Served as Eastern Area Secretary for Women's Work, United Presbyterian Church USA (UPCUSA) Foreign Mission Board.
1948 Traveled to Asia: taught at Tokyo Woman's Christian College, visited Korea, the Philippines and China.
1949 Joined Church of the Master in New York City; later became the first white elder.
1951-58 Director, Office of Student Work, UPCUSA (renamed Student World Relations in 1958).
1951 Assigned responsibility for Overseas Scholarship Program
1952-53 Nov.-Feb. Around-the-world trip for Youth Emphasis Year of Presbyterian Board of Foreign Missions (Japan, Hong Kong, Philippines, Thailand, India, Pakistan, Syria, Lebanon, Jordan, Iran, Iraq, Paris, Amsterdam, Switzerland); attended General Assembly of WSCF in Nasrapur, India.
1953 Chaired Youth Emphasis Year, UPCUSA Board of Foreign Missions.
1953 Initiated Junior Year Abroad Program.
1955 Chaired Planning Committee for 17th SVM (CWM) Quadrennial.
1958-68 Director, Office of Student World Relations.
1959 Chaired Planning Committee for 18th SVM (CWM) Quadrennial.
1960 Initiated Frontier Internship in Missions Program.
1960-68 Chaired WSCF Committee on Foreign Students.
1963-64 Initiated International Study Fellowship on the University Ministry at Princeton Seminary (WSCF).
1966-72 Chaired UPCUSA Committee on Internationalization of Mission; developed official policy for COEMAR.
1966-80+ Executive Secretary, Cooperating Committee for Tokyo Woman's Christian University.
1967-73 Chaired WSCF New Headquarters Committee.
1968 Sabbatical: study at Ecumenical Center in Bossey, Switzerland and CIDOC in Cuernavaca, Mexico.
1969-71 Special Assignment: New Dimensions in Mission, developing experimental missions programs (Presbyterian bureaucracy restructured).
1970 Initiated Bi-National Service Program.
1970 Initiated Politics and Theology Project.
1971 Initiated Transnational Consultations.
1971-1990 President, North American Trustees of the World Christian Student Federation
1972-1977 Associate for Human Resources Planning, Ministries Through People in Mission Unit of the Program Agency, UPCUSA.
1974 Oversaw transition of Frontier Internship Program to international administration.
1975-86 Association of Christians for Women's Education and Development in Asia, Asian Women's Institute
1976 Traveled to China.
1977-80 Associate for Ecumenical Patterns of Sharing, Ministries Through People in Mission Unit of the Program Agency, UPCUSA.
1978-82 Directed Education for Mission: Involvement for Mission Program (UPCUSA)
1979 Traveled to Cuba; taught ESL to church leaders.
1980 Retired from PCUSA National Staff.
1981 Minister in Residence, Pacific School of Religion, Berkeley, Cal.
1981-88 Ecumenical Resource Person in Residence, Gilmor-Sloane House, Stony Point Center, New York.
1982 Led tour to China.
1988-2009 Remained active in retirement, including writing the books noted below. See Flory's autobiographical writings for more information
2004 May Margaret's 90th birthday was celebrated by a party at Riverside Church, NY and a weekend symposium.
2009 Oct 1 Died in North Carolina
Scope and Contents
The collection documents the career of Margaret Flory, ecumenist, leader in student religious work, and mission executive in the Presbyterian Church (USA) from 1944-1980 who established and directed innovative programs including Junior Year Abroad, Frontier Internships in Mission, and Bi-National Service. This collection complements a number of archival collections in the YDSL archives including the archives of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions, the World Student Christian Federation, and the Asian Women's Institute. The Flory papers illustrate how the workings of various ecumenical mission and student organizations intersected and overlapped in the activities of one committed representative. This record of the career of an ambitious and creative proponent of international missions, university ministry, and the ecumenical movement makes a valuable contribution to the YDSL archive's emphases on Protestant missions and Christian student movements.
The first twelve of the fifteen series in this collection represent organizations with which Flory was associated. While it seemed wise to establish these series in order to provide a structure for the collection, it should be noted that Flory was involved in numerous, overlapping activities throughout her career and many of these organizations intersected with each other in various ways. For example, the Student Study Seminars documented in Series IV were sponsored by the United Campus Christian Fellowship (Series VI), a part of the National Student Christian Federation (Series VI), which was in turn a member of the World Student Christian Federation (Series VII), but they were administered by Flory in her capacity as director of the Office of Student World Relations (Series I) of the Presbyterian Church (USA) (Series XI).
Flory's career was most centrally defined by her eighteen years (1951-68) as the director of the Office of Student World Relations (called Office of Student Work until 1958), part of the Board of Foreign Missions/Commission on Ecumenical Mission and Relations of the United Presbyterian Church, recorded in Series I. During this time, Flory started the Junior Year Abroad program for college juniors (1953; Series III) and the Frontier Internship in Mission program for recent graduates (1960; Series II) and directed a series of Student Seminars for the United Campus Christian Fellowship (Series IV). Her work also included organizing international service opportunities for the Association of Presbyterian University Pastors (Series V). Although administered under Presbyterian auspices, all of these programs served a broader, ecumenical constituency. The ecumenical and international nature of Flory's service to students naturally led to a high level of involvement with the ecumenical student movement, both in the United States (Series VI) and internationally (WSCF; Series VII), and with the education and mission programs of the National and World Councils of Churches (Series VIII).
After a transitional three-year assignment in New Dimensions in Mission (1969-71), Flory continued to serve in the newly-reorganized People in Mission Unit of the Presbyterian USA Program Agency as Associate for Human Resources. Although she no longer had the direct involvement with student programs that defined her prior assignment, her work continued to be shaped by the priorities and relationships she had developed in the Office of Student World Relations. She continued to oversee the Frontier Internship program until it made the transition to international administration in 1974, and she started a new program, Bi-National Servants (1971; Series IX), to encourage returned Frontier Interns and others with international experience to maintain their connection with their "country of relationship." She also oversaw programs including Mission to the USA, Three-Way Mission, and Overseas Associates, and served as president of the Association of North American Cooperating Agencies of Overseas Women's Christian Colleges for the Asian Women's Institute (Series X, see also AWI archives, RG 106). In 1978, she was called upon to lead an experimental program in Education for Mission: Involvement in Mission.
Series XI contains records of Flory's work for the Presbyterian Church other than through the Office of Student World Relations (Series I), including activities concurrent with her service in the OSWR but under other denominational structures, the latter third of her career with the People in Mission Unit, and post-retirement activities such as the 150 year celebration of Presbyterian Missions in 1987 and the Global Mission Conference in 1989. It also contains records related to divisions of the Presbyterian bureaucracy other than the missions board in which Flory was employed.
Flory's engagement with the other organizations in Series XII ranged from simply having received information about them in the course of her work to being a member to active leadership. Leadership roles held by Flory in these organizations are noted in the following contents listing.
Series XIII contains subject files and program resources collected by Flory in the course of her career, many of which relate to a number of the organizations covered in the first twelve series. For example, the internationalization of mission was a major interest of Flory, and there are internationalization files in most of the organizational Series I-XII, as well as general files on the topic of internationalization in Series XIII. Subject files may contain materials generated by, for, or about organizations represented in other series, but are filed here topically rather than by the organization name. The subject files convey major themes of Flory's ministry, such as her enduring interest in China and Latin America and her commitment to innovation in mission, to civil rights, and to student work.
Series XIV contains biographical materials and memorabilia, including materials from just some of Flory's extensive travels. Of note is the record of the "Friends of Margaret Flory" event in Nov. 1980 to mark her so-called retirement (Flory found the term "retirement" an ill fit, since she remained at least as active in ministry after retirement as before). This event included a one-day symposium on "The International and Ecumenical Task of the Church in the Next Two Decades," during which participants reflected on issues that had been key concerns in Flory's career. The issues selected for these discussions provide an apt summary of some of the major themes treated in this archive:
Church and University
Student Movement
Peace Making
Internationalization of Mission
Women's Role
Church in Socialist Countries
Human Rights
Ecumenical Movement
Education for Mission
Racism/International Ecumenical Community
BIBLIOGRAPHY
Flory, Margaret, "Christmas at Stony Point," Outreach, Dec. 1951 [Box 76-728a].
Flory, Margaret, "Drama with a Mission," Presbyterian Survey, Aug. 1953 [Box 94-1050a].
Flory, Margaret, "Encounter in Study and Fellowship," Federation News, May-Aug. 1957 (no. 3-4), 73-78 [Box 21-113c].
Flory, Margaret, "New Patterns of Obedience in Mission," Concern, June-July 1960, 24-25 [Box 39-245a].
Flory, Margaret, "A New Ministry in a New World," Concern, October 1963 [Box 127-1367]
Flory, Margaret, "The Same Gospel: A Changing Context," Horizons, Nov.-Dec. 1988, 12-13 [Box 78-762a].
Flory, Margaret, "What Are Frontier Internships?" Concern, May 1962 (Thank Offering Issue), 3-4 [Box 13-76].
Flory, Margaret and Alice Hageman, The University, the Church and Internationalization, St. Louis: UMHE Publications Office, 1968 [Box 95-1063b].
Todd, Kathleen, ed., Crossing Boundaries: Stories from the Frontier Internship in Mission Programme, Geneva: WCC Mission Series, No. 5, 1985.
Flory, Margaret, Moments in time: one woman's ecumenical journey. New York: Friendship Press, c1995. [Box 110]
Flory, Margaret, From Past to Future: Experiments in Global Bridging. New York: The History Project, World Student Christian Federation, c1997 [Box 110]
Flory, Margaret, FIM in the Beginning. FIM Mission Series (pamphlet excerpt from From Past to Future .)
Flory, Margaret, Dear house: mission becomes you: Gilmor Sloane House, Stony Point, New York, 1949-1999. Louisville, Ky.: Bridge Resources, c2000. [Box 110]
Arrangement
I. Office of Student World Relations (United Presbyterian Church, USA)
II. Frontier Internships in Mission
III. Junior Year Abroad
IV. Student Study Seminars (UCCF/NSCF)
V. Association of Presbyterian University Pastors
VI. Ecumenical Student Movement in the United States
VII. World Christian Student Federation
VIII. National and World Councils of Churches
IX. Bi-National Service
X. Asian Women's Institute
XI. United Presbyterian Church, USA
XII. Other Organizations
XIII. Collected Materials
XIV. Personal Items and Memorabilia
XV. Audio-Visual Materials
Church work with students; Ecumenists -- United States; Presbyterians -- United States; Flory, Margaret; Asian Women's Institute; World Student Christian Federation; World's Student Christian Federation
- Student World Relations (SWR), Series I
  - Memoranda, reports, etc., 1951-1970
    - General, 1950-1958 (Box 1A, Folder 1-3)
    - Survey of Student Work in Africa, Middle East, Asia, Europe and Latin America, 1958 (Box 1A, Folder 3a)
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 1A, Folder 4-6)
    - General, 1963-1966 (Box 1B, Folder 7-7b)
    - "OMEGA" Files, 1966-1968 May (Box 1B, Folder 7b1-7b5)
    - "OMEGA" Files, Jun-Oct, 1968 (Box 1C, Folder 7b6)
    - General, 1967-1970 (Box 1C, Folder 7b7)
    - Study-Work Fellowship Application Reference Form, n.d. (Box 1C, Folder 7b8)
  - Office Budgets
    - General, 1965-1967 (Box 1C, Folder 7c-8)
  - Fraternal Workers Program
    - Philip, T.V., 1957-1963 (Box 1C, Folder 8a-8c)
    - Robb, Dale, 1953-1962 (Box 1C, Folder 8c-8e)
    - Robb, Dale, et. al - 2001 Survey: Presbyterian Campus Ministry 1924-1973, The Westminster Foundation, Oxford, Ohio (Box 1C, Folder 8e)
    - Seel, Robert, 1956-1962 (Box 1d, Folder 8f)
    - Sheldon, Ben, 1956-1959 (Box 1d, Folder 8g)
    - Sutarno, 1960-1963 (Box 1d, Folder 8h)
    - Thorp, Robert, 1954-1959 (Box 1d, Folder 8i)
    - Thurber, L. Newton, 1959-1961 (Box 1d, Folder 8j)
    - Todd, George E., 1959-1963 (Box 1d, Folder 9)
  - Mailings to Overseas Student Workers, 1955-1966
    - Mailings, 1955-1963 (Box 1d, Folder 9a-9f)
    - Mailings, 1963-1966 (Box 1E, Folder 9g-9i)
    - Literature Orders and Invoices, 1966 (Box 1E, Folder 9i1)
    - Master Mailing Lists, 1956-1969 (Box 1E, Folder 9j)
  - World Family Circle
    - Directories, 1960-1965 (Box 1E, Folder 9j1-9l)
    - Directories, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9m-9o)
  - Correspondence Files 1956-1965
    - A-B (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
    - Busse (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - C (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Costa (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Day (Box 2, Folder 16-16a)
    - De-Dirks (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Divas (Box 3, Folder 18-18a)
    - Dotson, Paul (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
    - Downs, Ray (Box 3, Folder 21-21a)
    - F (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Flory, Margaret -- Speaking Engagements, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 22a-22d)
    - Flory, Margaret -- Travel, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 22e)
    - G (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Galland, V. (Box 4, Folder 23a)
    - General, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 23b-23d)
    - H (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Hahn, Christopher (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Hoffman, Cecil (Box 4a, Folder 26-26a)
    - I-K (Box 4a, Folder 27)
    - International Studies Program (Box 4a, Folder 27a)
    - L (Box 4a, Folder 28)
    - M-R (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
    - Roy, Andrew T. (Box 5, Folder 30a)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 31-31a)
    - Seto, Paul (Missionary Associate), 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 31a1)
    - Sikakane, Enos Z. (Box 5, Folder 31b-31d)
    - T (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Thorp, Robert C. (Box 5, Folder 32a)
    - Thurber, L. Newton (Box 5, Folder 32b)
    - U-Z (Box 5a, Folder 32c-32d)
    - W-Z (Box 5a, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence File 1966
    - A-B (Box 5a, Folder 33-34a)
    - Black (Box 5a, Folder 34b)
    - C-D (Box 5a, Folder 35-37)
    - Duley, John (Box 5a, Folder 37a)
    - E-F (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Fil-American Team (Box 6, Folder 38a)
    - Frelick, Paul (John Knox House, Geneva, SU) (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - G (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - George, P. J. (Box 6, Folder 40a)
    - H-K (Box 6, Folder 41-43a)
    - L-M (Box 7, Folder 44-46)
    - Morton, D. (Conscientious Objector) (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - N-R (Box 7, Folder 48-50)
    - S-W (Box 8, Folder 51-56)
    - Wilson, Donald (Box 8, Folder 56a)
    - Y-Z (Box 8, Folder 56b)
    - Yale in China (Box 8, Folder 56c)
    - Yolton, William (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence File, 1967
    - A-B (Box 9, Folder 57a-57c)
    - Bloom, Bill (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - C (Box 9, Folder 5.7E-56)
    - Carino, Fely (Box 9, Folder 57g)
    - D (Box 9, Folder 57h)
    - E-F (Box 10, Folder 57i)
    - Faggeter, Rachel (Box 10, Folder 57j)
    - G (Box 10, Folder 57k)
    - Galland, Valdo (Box 10, Folder 57l)
    - General (Box 10, Folder 57m)
    - H-M (Box 10, Folder 57n-57q)
    - N-T (Box 10a, Folder 57r-57w)
    - Telesca, Mrs. Edna (Box 10a, Folder 57x)
    - U-Z (Box 10a, Folder 57y-57z)
    - Yolton, William (Box 10a, Folder 57z1)
  - Correspondence File 1968
    - A-B (Box 11, Folder 58-59a)
    - Brown, Rex E. (Box 11, Folder 59b)
    - C-L (Box 11, Folder 60-67)
    - M-Z (Box 12, Folder 68-75)
    - Yolton, William (Box 12, Folder 75a)
- Frontier Internships in Mission Program (FIM), Series II
  - Program Overview
    - Publications, promotional, commemorative, 1960-1987 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Application/Evaluation Forms (Blank), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76a)
    - Guidelines Handbooks (Box 13, Folder 76b)
    - Intern Lists, up to 1975 (Box 13, Folder 76c)
    - Directories, 1995, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 1317)
    - Directory, 1998-1999 (Box 117, Folder 1318)
  - Frontier Intern Library: Bibliographies
    - General, 1968, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Africa, 1965, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76e)
    - Asia, 1967-1968, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Europe, 1963, 1968, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76g)
    - Latin America, 1964, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76h)
    - Middle East, 1965, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76i)
    - Urbanization, 1963, 1967, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 76j)
  - General Files, 1960-1971
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Intern Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 77a)
    - General, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 77b)
    - General, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Evaluation for WSCF, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 78a)
    - Intern Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 78b)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 78c)
    - Larry Miller Article, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Evaluations, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 7.8E-77)
    - General, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Evaluations, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 79a)
    - Evaluation Conference, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 79b-79d)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 119, Folder 1335)
    - General, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Orientation Workbook, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 80a)
    - Request for FIM Appointment, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 1336)
    - General, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 81-84)
    - Project Application, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 1334)
    - General, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Ten-Year FIM Program Evaluation
    - Program Evaluation, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 86-89)
    - Ten-Year Evaluation, Margaret Flory, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 89a)
  - Frontier Intern (student) Evaluations of FIM Program 1971-1980
    - Evaluations, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 90-91)
  - General Files 1971-1989
    - General, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 92-93)
    - Asia Re-entry Project, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 93a)
    - Assignment Possibilities, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 93b)
    - General, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 94-96)
    - Finances, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 96a)
    - General, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 97-100)
    - General, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 101-104)
    - Interim Committees, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104a)
    - International Working Party -- Preparatory Materials, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104b)
    - International Working Party -- Preparatory Materials (Copy 2), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104c)
    - International Working Party -- Report, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - International Working Party -- Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104e)
    - Revision of Forms, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Nominations, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 104g)
    - International Coordinating Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 104h)
    - General, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 105-107)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 107a)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 1337)
    - Regional Committees, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 107b)
    - Project Applications, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 107c)
    - Finance, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Self-Evaluations, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 107e)
    - General, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 108-108a)
    - Insurance Information, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 108b)
    - General, 1976-1981 (Box 20, Folder 109-110a)
    - International Coordinating Committee, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 110b)
    - North American Committee, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 110c)
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 111)
    - re: FIM Book, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 111a)
    - General, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 111b-112a)
    - Blueprints Journal, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 112b)
    - General, 1988-1994 (Box 20, Folder 112c-112d)
    - General, 1995-1996 (Box 117, Folder 1319)
    - Programme, Operational Prospectus and Financial Audits for 1995 and 1996, 1997, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 1320)
    - Drafts of History (Box 117, Folder 1321)
    - Mission from the Reverse of History: A Brief History of Frontier Internship in Mission by Manuel Quintero, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 1322)
    - Lost interns, 1998- (Box 117, Folder 1323)
    - General, 1998-1999 (Box 117, Folder 1324)
    - Fortieth Anniversary Celebration and International Coordinating Committee Meeting, Havana, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1325)
    - Fortieth Anniversary Celebration and International Coordinating Committee Meeting, Havana. Workbook Part One, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1326)
    - Fortieth Anniversary Celebration and International Coordinating Committee Meeting, Havana. Workbook Part Two, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1327)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 118, Folder 1328)
    - Cuba Trip, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1329)
    - Casebook -- Drafts, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 1330)
    - Programme, Operational Prospectus and Financial Audit for 1998, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 1331)
    - Programme, Operational Prospectus and Financial Audit for 1999, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 1332)
    - Do Justice, Love Mercy: Justice in 21st Century, Essays to Mark the 40th Anniversary of FIM, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 1338)
    - Programme, Operational Prospectus and Financial Audit for 2000, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 1333)
    - FIM in the Beginning by M. Flory, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1339)
- Junior Year Abroad (JYA) Program, Series III
  - Publications
    - General Promotional Publications, 1953-1970 (Box 21, Folder 113)
    - Program Handbooks, 1953-1970 (Box 21, Folder 113a)
    - JYA Application Forms, materials, Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 113b)
    - Participant Lists, 1953-1965 (Box 21, Folder 113c)
    - "Invisible Bridges", 1953-1962 (Box 21, Folder 114-115)
    - "Invisible Bridges": submissions, photos, correspondence in re, 1952-1962 (Box 21, Folder 115a)
    - "Junior Year Abroad Letters" (solicited, promotional correspondence with students) edited excerpts for distribution, and some originals, 1954-1960 (Box 21, Folder 116)